[
  {
    "name": "Maths",
    "id": "food",
    "theme": "green",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "What is the value of sin(30)",
        "options": [
          "1/2",
          "3/2",
          "1/3",
          "1/4"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is?",
        "options": [
          "25.30",
          " 25.5",
           "25.00",
           "12.25"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
       {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Who was the one to discover zero?",
        "options": [
          "Newton",
          "Jeff Goldblum",
          "Aaryabhatta",
          "Shrinivasan Ramanujahn"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "In which American State did chili con carne originate?",
        "answer": "Texas"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If log 27 = 1.431, then the value of log 9 is?",
        "options": [
          "0.934",
          "0.945",
          "0.958",
          "0.954"
        ],
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What is the correct name for a cluster or bunch of bananas?",
        "options": [
          "Foot",
          "Hand",
          "Flock",
          "Pod"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "#include<stdio.h> gets replaced by the contents of the file stdio.h",
        "options": [
          "During editing",
         	"During linking",
        	"During execution",
       "	During preprocessing"
        ],
        "answer": 4
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Computer",
    "id": "knowledge",
    "theme": "pink",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What is the size of ‘int’?",
        "answer": "Compiler dependent"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "In DOS, how many bytes exist for near, far and huge pointers?",
        "options": [
           "Near: 2, far: 4, huge: 7",
           
		   "near: 4, far: 2, huge: 8",

           "near: 2, far: 4, huge: 4",

           "near: 4, far: 0, huge: 0"
        ],
        "answer": "3"
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Select the names of “The Three Musketeers”.",
        "options": [
          "Chevy",
          "Topeka",
          "Athos",
          "Duke",
          "Porthos",
          "John Felton",
          "Aramis"
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "toggle-translate",
        "question": "Which is the correct translation of Zorro?",
        "options": [
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Dog"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Sword"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Fox"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Coyote"
          ]
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If a 5,000 coupon bond has a coupon rate of 13 percent, then the coupon payment every year is ___",
        "options": [
          "650",
          "1,300",
          "None of These",
          "130"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many counters does a backgammon player have?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 15
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "There is a patron saint of The Internet.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "alpha-picker",
        "question": " Which letter other than X scores 8 in Scrabble?",
        "answer": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Four of the worst ten maritime disasters all took place in 1945. In which sea were all four ships sunk?",
        "options": [
          "Mediterranean sea",
          "Baltic Sea",
          "The Bermuda Triangle",
          "Black Sea"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is ",
        "options": [
          "25.30",
          "25.50",
          "25.00",
          "12.25"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Science",
    "id": "knowledge",
    "theme": "yellow",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Mole is a popular paste in Mexico. Mole is a mixture of chili’s and what other tasty ingredient?",
        "answer": "Chocolate"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What is the name of the famous art deco skyscraper in New York City?",
        "options": [
          "Trump Tower",
          "Chrysler building",
          "Empire State Building",
          "The New York Times Building"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Select the names of “The Three Musketeers”.",
        "options": [
          "Chevy",
          "Topeka",
          "Athos",
          "Duke",
          "Porthos",
          "John Felton",
          "Aramis"
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "toggle-translate",
        "question": "Which is the correct translation of Zorro?",
        "options": [
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Dog"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Sword"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Fox"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Coyote"
          ]
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If a 5,000 coupon bond has a coupon rate of 13 percent, then the coupon payment every year is ___",
        "options": [
          "650",
          "1,300",
          "None of These",
          "130"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many counters does a backgammon player have?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 15
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "There is a patron saint of The Internet.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "alpha-picker",
        "question": " Which letter other than X scores 8 in Scrabble?",
        "answer": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Four of the worst ten maritime disasters all took place in 1945. In which sea were all four ships sunk?",
        "options": [
          "Mediterranean sea",
          "Baltic Sea",
          "The Bermuda Triangle",
          "Black Sea"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is ",
        "options": [
          "25.30",
          "25.50",
          "25.00",
          "12.25"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Computer",
    "id": "known",
    "theme": "pink",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What is the size of ‘int’?",
        "answer": "Compiler dependent"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "In DOS, how many bytes exist for near, far and huge pointers?",
        "options": [
           "Near: 2, far: 4, huge: 7",
           
		      "near: 4, far: 2, huge: 8",

           "near: 2, far: 4, huge: 4",

           "near: 4, far: 0, huge: 0"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Select the names of “The Three Musketeers”.",
        "options": [
          "Chevy",
          "Topeka",
          "Athos",
          "Duke",
          "Porthos",
          "John Felton",
          "Aramis"
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "toggle-translate",
        "question": "Which is the correct translation of Zorro?",
        "options": [
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Dog"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Sword"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Fox"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Coyote"
          ]
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If a 5,000 coupon bond has a coupon rate of 13 percent, then the coupon payment every year is ___",
        "options": [
          "650",
          "1,300",
          "None of These",
          "130"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many counters does a backgammon player have?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 15
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "There is a patron saint of The Internet.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "alpha-picker",
        "question": " Which letter other than X scores 8 in Scrabble?",
        "answer": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Four of the worst ten maritime disasters all took place in 1945. In which sea were all four ships sunk?",
        "options": [
          "Mediterranean sea",
          "Baltic Sea",
          "The Bermuda Triangle",
          "Black Sea"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is ",
        "options": [
          "25.30",
          "25.50",
          "25.00",
          "12.25"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "History",
    "id": "history",
    "theme": "blue",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "The first words spoken on the moon by Buzz Aldrin were these:",
        "start": "Contact ",
        "answer": "Light"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The number of 3-digit numbers divisible by 6, is",
        "options": [
          "149",
          "166",
          "150",
          "151"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Average of three person’s age is 9 years. Find the sum of there age",
        "options": [
          "18",
          "21",
          "24",
          "27"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Which number is missing? 1, 9, 25, 49, (?)",
        "options": [
          "121",
          "81",
          "16",
          "169"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Which least number should be added to 2600 to make it a perfect square?",
        "options": [
          "3",
          "39",
          "1",
          "5"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "A clock seen through a mirror shows 8 o’clock. What is the correct time?",
        "options": [
          "8:00",
          "4:00",
          "12.20",
          "12.40"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If David’s age is 27 years old in 2011. What was his age in 2003?",
        "options": [
          "17 years",
          "37 years",
          "20 years",
          "19 years"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "What is 7% equal to?",
        "options": [
          "0.007",
          "0.07",
          "0.7",
          "7"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "0.05 × 0.09 × 5 = ___",
        "options": [
          "0.005",
          "0.0225",
          "0.025",
          "0.225"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If 5 boys take 7 hours to pack 35 cartoons, then how many boys can pack 65 cartoons in 3 hours?",
        "options": [
          "26",
          "39",
          "45",
          "None of These"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "106 × 106 – 94 × 94 = ?",
        "options": [
          "2004",
          "2400",
          "1904",
          "1906"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which states did the United States gain after the Mexican War?",
        "options": [
          "Arizona",
          "New Mexico",
          "Louisiana",
          "California",
          "Nevada",
          "Utah",
          "Texas"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          3,
          6
        ]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  }
]
